Greetings to all of you at the ICPO. I am L.
ICPO の皆様…
L です
Whether there's one or more culprits involved, the probability of them being Japanese is extremely high.
犯人は複数であれ単独であれ、
日本人である可能性が極めて高い
Whether there's one or more culprits involved, the probability of them being Japanese is extremely high.
Kira, I can guess what your motivation for doing this might be, but what you're doing is evil!
キラ、お前がどのような考えで、このような事をしているのか、
大体想像はつく
Kira, I can guess what your motivation for doing this might be, but what you're doing is evil!
しかし、お前のしている事は…悪だ！
You bastard!
コ、コイツ…
Try and kill me!
さぁ、私を殺してみろ
僕は「正義」だ！
I am justice!
どうした？
What's going on?
なんだこれは
悪に怯える弱い者を救い…
はやくやってみろ
I save the weak from evil, and I will become the God of a world that everyone desires!
すごい事になってるぞ
This is spiralling out of control!
さぁ早く
誰もが理想とする新世界の…
キラ対 L だってよ
今ここにいるんだ
途中中継だぜ…
神となる男だ！
L..
L …
Kira..
キラ…
I'll hunt you down.. and kill you!
必ずお前お探し出して…
必ずお前を探し出して…
I'll hunt you down.. and kill you!
始末する！
僕が…
I am..
私が…
JUSTICE!
正義だ！
The Deal
Atrocious Serial Murder Case
Special Investigative Headquarters
では、一般情報
Let's begin with the Public Intelligence report.
Yes.
はい
今日まで、電話などによる一般からの情報は3029件あり、
The total number of reports from the public, including phone calls, currently stands at 3029.
Unfortunately, the large majority of them seems to be prank calls.
そのほとんどが野次馬的な物はばかりですが…
There have been 14 reported incidents of people who either know or have seen Kira.
「キラを知っている」、「キラを見た」という情報が14件あります
We have investigated these thoroughly, one by one, and I believe that - just as reported - it would be safe to say that none of them have any credibility.
一つ一つ丁寧に対応して記録しましたが…
報告書のとおりで、信憑性のあるものはなしと言っていいと思います
There are also 21 reported incidents of people claiming to be Kira.
それからほかに、
「自分がキラである」と言ってきた者が21件あります
ん？
Each of those 21 reports has been followed up, and will remain on file.
すべての可能性を捨てず、
その２１人全員の調書をとってファイルしています
うん、では次、
Moving onto the victims..
被害者
Yes.
はい
We can confirm that information on all the known victims that died of heart attacks was publicly available in Japan.
今まで明らかになった、
被害者と思われる心臓麻痺死者のすべては、
日本で情報を得ることが可能だった者と、裏づけが取れました
In addition, we have followed up L's specific request that we investigate the assumed time of death for each victim.
そして、 L から特に調査を要望されていた死亡推定時刻ですが…
Results indicate that 68% of all deaths occurred during weekdays, between four in the afternoon and midnight, Japanese time.
日本時間の平日午後四時頃から、深夜二時
特に午後８時から午前零時がその６８％です
The number of deaths peaks over the weekend, when they can occur at any time between eleven in the morning through till late at night.
そして、土、日、祝日は、
午前１１時から深夜まで、かなりのばらつきがあります
This is all extremely interesting information.
非常に興味深い情報です
It suggests that given the assumed times of death, there is a possibility that our culprit may be a student.
もしかしたら、その死亡推定時刻から、
犯人は学生である可能性がありますね
I do have further grounds to support this.
根拠はまだあります
Given that they appear to be only targeting criminals, the culprit seems to be motivated by a sense of "justice".
犯罪者ばかり殺している事から、
犯人は彼なりの正義感に基づいて行動している
It's conceivable that they may even plan on becoming some kind of God.
もしかしたら、神にでもなるつもりなのかもしれません
This means that we may be dealing with an extremely hollow psychology.
これは非常に幼稚の心理といわざるを得ません
しかしまさか…
Of course, this is mere speculation.
これはあくまでも可能性の話です
However, please rid yourselves of any preconceptions you might have that our culprit cannot be a student.
しかし、
学生が犯人なわけがないといった、固定観念は捨ててください
However, please rid yourselves of any preconceptions you might have that our culprit cannot be a student.
To consider every possibility; that is likely to be the shortest road to apprehending Kira.
あらゆる可能性を摸索する事、
それがキラ逮捕への近道になるはずです
To consider every possibility; that is likely to be the shortest road to apprehending Kira.
Please continue the investigation report.
捜査報告を続けてください
え、ええ…
Y-Yes.
Are there any other observations?
何か他に気づいた者は？
Umm.. Yes.
あ…はい
What is it, Matsuda?
何だ、松田
あ…
I don't mean to support Kira in any way by saying this..
これは、キラを肯定する意味では絶対ありません、が…
この数日世界的に…
but over the last few days.. throughout the world, but especially in Japan.. the number of serious crimes committed have dramatically decreased.
特に日本でですが…
強盗以上の凶悪犯罪が激減しています
but over the last few days.. throughout the world, but especially in Japan.. the number of serious crimes committed have dramatically decreased.
I guess.. that kind of phenomenon was to be expected..
まぁ…
当たり前と言えば、当たり前の現象かもしれんな…
Anything else?
他には？
今日の捜査報告はこんなところです
Right. L, that concludes today's investigation report.
L
Good work. I feel that we're one step closer to finding the culprit.
お疲れ様です
また少し犯人に近づけた気がします
Good work. I feel that we're one step closer to finding the culprit.
Also, I have another order to trouble you with.
そして、また注文で申し訳ないのですが…
I need the teams investigating victims, information and Internet to double-check what information regarding each victim was previously released in Japan.
特に被害者班、報道班、インターネット班に、
犠牲になった者が、
日本でどのような報道のされ方をしていたのかを、
もう一度よく調べていただきたい
More specifically, whether or not footage or photographs of the victims had been released.
知りたいのは、
犠牲者の顔写真や、映像が出ていたかどうかです
Thank you.
よろしくお願いします
Chief!
局長
ん？
You're looking pretty tired.
ずいぶんとお疲れのようですね
Ah, thanks. The late nights are beginning to take their toll on me.
あぁ…悪いな
ここんのところ徹夜続きだからな…
Ah, thanks. The late nights are beginning to take their toll on me.
Thinking about this now, everyone was probably already aware of what I said about crime going down.
犯罪が減ってるって発言…
考えてみれば、みんなわかってることなのに…
すみません…
I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
何を言ってるんだ
どんなことでも、事実はどんどん発言しろ
Continue to speak the truth, no matter what kind of truth it may be.
Especially when it's awkward to say.
人が言いにくそうなことなら尚更だ
もっとも、
「犯罪を減らした功績を讃えて、キラを表彰しよう」なんて続いたら、
In fact, if everyone continues to think that Kira should be commended for lowering crime, it will become harder and harder to say it out loud.
問題発言になったかもしれんかな
S-Surely no one would commend such a murderer?
ま…まさか、あの殺人鬼を?!
はははは…冗談だ
I'm joking.
I knew I could count on you, onii-chan.
さすがお兄ちゃん
って、お前自分で理解できたのか？
So do you understand?
Err.. Yeah, sort of.
えっ？
うん…まぁまぁ
Sounds like dad's back.
あ、お父さん帰ってきたみたい
Welcome home, darling.
あなた、お帰りなさい
うん
He's back early today.
今日は早いね
Hey! Why don't you at least try doing the last question yourself?
おい、最後の問題ぐらい自分で解いてみろよ
I will. After dinner.
ご飯のあとでね
Jeez..
ったく…
You must have everything in hand, seeing you're able to afford the time to help out with your sister's homework.
妹の勉強の面倒なんて余裕あるな
Yeah.
ああ
Even if the police were to come after me, I'm confident that I have something to fight them with.
僕が警察が動いても戦える、ひとつの自信があるからね
Welcome home, father.
お帰りなさい、
父さん
Ahh.. Yes, I'm back.
あ…ただいま
How are your studies going, Light?
月、勉強のほうはどうだ？
ん？まぁまぁだよ
Not bad.
Same as always. Top of the year.
いつもどおり学年トップ、自慢の兄です、はい
I'm so proud of my older brother! Yes!
I'm so proud of my son! Yes!
自慢の息子です、はい
You seem tired, father.
父さん、疲れてるみたいだね
あ…詳しい事は言えないが、
I'm not allowed to say much, but this case is proving to be exceedingly difficult.
今回の事件は難しいからな
I see.
なるほど…
Your father is part of the police force.
父親が警察の人間、
So this is the source of your confidence, Light.
それがお前の自信というわけか、ライト
Yeah.
ああ、自分のパソコンから、何の痕跡も残さず
I can also access my father's computer without leaving any trace.
父さんのパソコンに侵入する事さえできるよ
So I can get hold of all the information regarding the investigation, anytime.
捜査状況を常に把握できるんだ
Here we go.
来た
It seems that the police are already beginning to suspect that the culprit could be a student.
警察はすでに、犯人は学生でないかと疑い始めているな…
Won't that be risky for you, Light?
やばいんじゃないか、ライト
"If the cause of death is written within 40 seconds of writing the person's name, it will happen as it is written."
「名前のあとに、４０秒以内に死因を書くとそのとおりになる。
"If the cause of death is not specified, then by default, the person will die of a heart attack."
死因を書かなければ、すべてが心臓麻痺となる」
"Should a cause of death be specified, a further 6 minutes 40 seconds are granted to write any further details."
「死因を書くとさらに６分４０秒、
詳しい死の状況を記載する時間が与えられる」
That's correct, isn't it Ryuk?
…だったね、リュック？
Yeah.. So what?
それがどうした？
In other words, if you write "heart attack" first, you can still write details of their death afterwards.
つまり、心臓麻痺という死因を書けば、
そのあとに死の状況、あるいは死亡時刻なども書けるわけだ
In other words, if you write "heart attack" first, you can still write details of their death afterwards.
Looks like I'll be able to provide you with some more entertainment, Ryuk.
また少し、リュークを楽しませてあげられるかもね
ん？どうした？148番
Hey! What's going on?
Pull yourself together!
しっかりしろ！
What?!
なに？
ま…また昨日も心臓麻痺の犠牲者が、23人?!
T-There were another 23 victims yesterday?
Yes.
は…はい
There were 23 victims the day before that too.
一昨日の犠牲者も23人…
All spaced out evenly, one every hour.
きっかり１時間おきに一人ずつ…
The fact that this has continued over two weekdays must mean..
平日に二日もこれが続くということは…
The theory that the culprit could be a student is weakened..
犯人が学生って線は怪しくなってきたな
But anyone can potentially skip two days of school..
いや、学校を二日休むなんて誰でも…
That's not it!
そうではない
あ…
It's true that the likelihood of them being a student has gone down.
確かに学生の線は薄くなりました
But this is not what Kira is trying to say here.
が、キラの言いたいことはそんなことではない
Why have they spaced the killings at precisely one hour intervals?
なぜ１時間おきなのか？
And, why are the victims all prisoners that could be found quickly after their deaths?
そして、なぜ犠牲者が死んだら
すぐにわかる刑務所内の犯罪者に限られているのか…
And, why are the victims all prisoners that could be found quickly after their deaths?
Kira is trying to tell us.. that they can control the time of death at will.
キラはこう言っているんです：
「自分は死の時間を、自由に操れる」もんだ
馬鹿な…
But something strange is going on.
しかし妙だ…
As soon as the possibility that Kira could be a student was put forward, the timing of the murders change to indicate that this was not the case.
キラは学生かもしれないという疑いが生じたとたん、
それを否定するような殺人が起こった
A coincidence?
偶然か…？いや、それにしてはタイミング怪すぎる
No, the timing is too convenient.
Kira must have access to police information.
キラは警察の情報を知っているということか…
This is clearly... a direct challenge to me.
これは明らかに…
私への挑戦…
This is clearly... a direct challenge to me.
I think that L will probably begin to sweat a little.
今頃 L のやつ、焦ってると思うよ
I still have 50 criminals that I've deliberately left alive for a time like this.
こういう時の為にわざと残してある犯罪者が、まだ50人はいる
ほう…？
Plus, thanks to the last few incidents L should be beginning to suspect someone in, or connected to, the police.
そして今回のことで、 L は警察関係者を疑い始めているはず
Kira has a way of getting police information.
キラは捜査本部の情報を得る手段を持っている
This fact can no longer be ignored.
この事実を素通りにはできない
What is Kira's final objective?
キラの本当の狙いは何だ…
What are they trying to do?
奴は…何をしようとしている
I don't get it.
でもわからないな
Surely, showing them that you have connections to the police place you at a greater disadvantage than having them suspect Kira of being a student?
学生の線を消すより
警察に精通していると思われる方がよっぽと不利じゃないか
The answer to that is, I did it to help me find and destroy L.
その答えは…
L を探し出し…始末するためだ
What do ya mean?
どういうことだ
In this world, there are very few people who actually trust each other.
この人間社会で、
本当に信頼しあってる人間なんて…ほんの僅かさ
Even amongst the police force.. and especially between the police and L, who never had a bond of trust between them from the beginning.
それが警察という枠の中でも…
ましてや警察と L…
信頼関係なんて最初からないに等しい
Can you honestly trust someone whose name and face are unknown to you?
顔も名前もわからない奴を信用できるか？
Now that L knows that I'm getting police information, without a doubt, he'll try to find a trail leading to me that starts within the police force.
僕に捜査状況が洩れたと知った L は…
警察内部から、僕への糸口をつかもうとするに決まっている
When that happens, it'll only be a matter of time before even the police can't keep quiet with respect to L.
そうならば警察だって…
L に対して黙っていないのも時間の問題だ
On the outside, L and the police appear to be working together to catch me.
L と警察は、
表面上は協力し合い、僕を捕まえようとしている…
But behind the scenes, L will be investigating the police, and the police will be investigating L!
しかし裏では…
L は警察を調べ、警察は L を調べ出す
But behind the scenes, L will be investigating the police, and the police will be investigating L!
L を探し出すのは僕じゃない
I won't be the one who'll find L.. the police will do that for me.
警察が L を突き止める…
Then.. I'll erase him.
そして僕が… L を消す
What the hell is this?!
何だこれは？
Letter of
resignation
As you can see, they are letters of resignation.
見ての通り、辞表です
他の事件に回して頂くか、
Unless we're moved to a different case, we're leaving the police force.
それができなければ、警察を辞めます
But.. why?
な…何故だ…？
何故って…命が惜しいからですよ
Why?
Because we value our lives.
L's theory is that Kira has some ESP-like power that allows them to kill without having to be there, right?
L の推理では…
キラは超能力のようなもので、
直接手を下さず、人を殺せる…でしたね
If I was Kira, I'd try to kill those who are trying to catch me.
私がキラなら…自分を捕まえようとする人間は、殺します
After all, if they get caught, they'll be killed.
捕まえれば、自分が死刑ですからね
We've already seen this from that incident on TV, when Kira killed the "dummy L" after being provoked.
前に L は…
テレビでキラに「私を殺してみろ」と、
スタンドプレーまがいの事をしてみせたじゃないですか？
We've already seen this from that incident on TV, when Kira killed the "dummy L" after being provoked.
But L hasn't even revealed his name, let alone his face!
でも L は、自分の名前どころか、顔すら出していない
That order we received earlier from L, about checking the information released about the victims prior to their deaths,
そしてこの間…
L が私たちに命じたのは、
犠牲になった者が、日本でどう報道されていたか
and whether or not footage or photos of their faces had been released.. That turned out to be true!
犠牲になった犯罪者の顔が、写真や映像で出ていたかどうかです
そのとおりでした！
Every single one of them had their photo published in Japan!
犠牲者は全員、日本の報道で顔が確認できたものでした
Unlike someone we all know; we had to investigate using our police IDs with our photos attached!
私たちは…誰かとは違って、
警察手帳という、
写真の入った身分証明書を持って捜査しているんです
Without hiding our faces!
堂々と、顔を隠さず
We could be killed by Kira at any time.
私たちは、キラにいつ殺されてもおかしくない…
That's why we're asking to be re-assigned.
これが部署移動を希望する理由です
Excuse us.
失礼いたします
Hey! You! Hold on a moment!
お…おい、君たち…
待ちたまえ！
Huh?
ん？
In order to solve this problem we must first establish the concept that x squared equals large X.
え…まずこの問題の解き方の発想ですが…
x 二乗…
イコール…
X  …
とおいて得られる、X の二次方程式が、正の理解を持つ事を示すという方法で考えます
You can then proceed by noting that the quadratic equation in large X is the key to understanding the problem..
与えられると…
FBI には四日前から日本に入ってもらい、
We had the FBI arrive in Japan four days ago.
They've begun their investigation of the Japanese police force.
警察関係者を調べてもらっています
These are the people on the list?
それがこのリストだな
Affirmative.
はい
警察の中だけでも、
There are 141 people within the police who have access to information regarding Kira.
キラの捜査情報を得られた者も141人
But within the 141 people, or people close to them.. Kira will definitely be amongst them.
しかしこの141人の中、
あるいはその身近なところに…
But within the 141 people, or people close to them.. Kira will definitely be amongst them.
必ずキラはいる
Hey, Light. Got a moment?
ライト…
ちょっといいか？
Hey, Light. Got a moment?
極力、外では話をかけるなって言っただろう
How many times do I have to tell you not to talk to me in public?
何度言えばわかる
Okay, in that case, I'll just talk at you.
じゃ、一方的に話すぞ
If you don't wanna listen, just cover your ears or something.
聞きたくなかったら耳でも塞げ
オレはライトが嫌いじゃないし、
I don't dislike you.
ある意味最高の奴にノートを拾われたと思っている
In some ways I think the notebook was found by an awesome person, because I have to remain by your side until either you or that Death Note expires.
何故なら、
ノートの最後が、
ライトの最後を見届けなくてはならないからだ
But.. I'm not on your side, and I'm not going to be on L's side either.
しかし…オレはライトの味方でも、L の味方でもない
I know that much already, Ryuk.
わかってたよそれぐらい、リュック
That's why I'll never say that what you're doing is right or wrong.
だからオレは、
ライトがやってる事が正しいとか正しくないとか、
そんな事はこれからも一切言わない
Although as your roommate, I may have a few things to say.
もっとも、同居人としての口出しはするがな
What's up, Ryuk?
どうしたんだよリュック？今更そんな事を言い出して…
Why are you saying things like this now? It's not like you.
らしくないぞ
Therefore what I'm about to say is not because I'm on Kira's side, but because it's giving me the creeps.
だから今からオレが言う事は、キラの味方として言うのではなく、
オレ自身が気持ち悪いから言うんだが…
Therefore what I'm about to say is not because I'm on Kira's side, but because it's giving me the creeps.
Quit beating around the bush.
回りくどいな…
There's a human following you.
ずっとお前をつけている人間がいる…
He's been bugging me lately.
目障りなんだよここんとこ
Although I know he can't see me, but because I'm always following you around, it kinda feels like I'm being watched.
あいつにはオレは見えていないが、
いつもお前の後ろにいるオレとしては、常に見られている気分だ…
Although I know he can't see me, but because I'm always following you around, it kinda feels like I'm being watched.
Looks like I've got a problem.
それは邪魔だな
なるべく早く消してやるよ、リュック
I'll have to get rid of him as soon as possible, Ryuk.
Who the hell is he?
何者だ、一体…
L が…警察を疑い出したという事か
Does this mean that L has already started to suspect the police?
Whoever is investigating the police must have large resources.
警察を調べるのなら、相当の人数のはずだ
仮に50人で調べたとしても…
Even if they have 50 people on the case, the chances that they'll suspect I'm Kira are non-existent.
僕はキラだと疑われる可能性はまずない…
They shouldn't be looking at me as anything more than a final year student.
僕はただの受験生にしか見えていないはず…
But if I leave him alone for a few months, the probability that I'll be caught might rise above zero.
しかし、何ヶ月も放っておけば、
可能性はゼロではなくなるかもしれない…
まずはその尾行者の名前だ…
First I need my stalker's name.
If I can figure that out, I can take care of everything
それがわかれば、
すべて処理できる
ライト
Light... Let me tell you something cool.
いいことを教えてやろう
There are two very important differences between a Shinigami and a human with a Death Note.
死神とデスノートを持った人間とでは、
二つの大きな違いがある
Do you know why Shinigami write human names into their Death Note?
「なぜ死神がデスノートに人間の名前を書くか」
…知ってるか？
Of course I don't.
僕が知るわけないだろう
You're pretty talkative today, Ryuk.
今日は随分おしゃべりだな…リュック
It's because Shinigami take human life spans for themselves.
死神は人間の寿命をもらっているからだ
っあ？寿命をもらう？
Take their "life spans"?
人間界で普通に60歳まで生きる人間を、
For example, if you take someone due to die at 60, and write their name so they die at 40 instead..
40歳で死ぬようにノートに書く
Sixty minus forty, is twenty. Those twenty human years are added to that Shinigami's life span.
６０ － ４０ ＝ ２０
60引く40、イコール20
Sixty minus forty, is twenty. Those twenty human years are added to that Shinigami's life span.
その人間界での20年という時間が、死神の寿命にプラスされるんだ
だからよほど怠けてない限り、
So as long as we don't slack off too much, a Shinigami can't be killed with a bullet to the head, or a knife through the heart.
頭を拳銃でぶち貫かれようと、
心臓をナイフで刺されようと、死神は死なない
So as long as we don't slack off too much, a Shinigami can't be killed with a bullet to the head, or a knife through the heart.
However, if you write a human's name in the Death Note, Light, your life span won't increase.
しかし、ライトがデスノートに人間の名前を書いても、
ライトの寿命は伸びない
これが死神と、デスノートを持った人間との違いだ
That's one of the differences between a Shinigami and a human with a Death Note.
ふん～人間にとっては、死神の新説だね
Now that's a theory about Shinigami that humans haven't heard before.
ちょっとおもしろいよ
That's kind of interesting.
The second difference will probably be even more of an interest to you.
二つ目の違いは、多分、ライトにとってもっと面白い
Though it concerns decreasing life spans rather than increasing them.
寿命を延ばすではなく、縮める話だがな
Decreasing them?
縮める話？
A Shinigami can tell someone's name by just looking at them.
死神は人間の顔を見るだけで、その人間の名前がわかる
Do you know why?
なぜだかわかるか？
A Shinigami's eyes have the ability to see a person's name and life span by just looking at them.
死神の目には…
人間の顔を見ると、
そいつの名前と寿命が顔の上に見えるんだ
A Shinigami's eyes have the ability to see a person's name and life span by just looking at them.
Name and life span?
名前と、寿命…
Yagami Light
Of course, I can see your name and life span right now.
もちろん、今オレの目にはライトの名前と寿命が見えている
If I converted that into human time, you would know precisely how many human years you have.
人間の時間に直すと、何年かはっきりわかる
もちろん、そんなことは口が裂けても言えない
Of course, we aren't allowed to tell you that kind of stuff.
Not even a huge blabbermouth like me.
ここまで口の裂けているオレでもな…
Therefore, a Shinigami will never be prevented from killing someone due to not knowing their name.
だから死神は殺す奴の名前がわからなくて困る事はないし、
When they kill someone, they know exactly how much life they're gaining.
その人間を殺せば、
自分の寿命がどれだけ延びるかがはっきりわかる
Our eyes are different.
目が違う…それがオレとライトの決定的な違いだ
That's the distinct difference between you and me.
However, if a Shinigami drops a notebook, and a human picks it up.. the Shinigami can change that human's eyes into the eyes of a Shinigami.
そして、死神は自分の落としたノートを拾った人間の目を…
死神の目にしてやることができる
えっ？
That is, if you agree to the deal passed down for this purpose since ancient times.
古くから伝承されてきた取引をすれば…だ
Deal...?
取引…！
The price for the eyes of a Shinigami is.. half of that human's remaining life span.
目　玉
死神の眼球の値段は…
The price for the eyes of a Shinigami is.. half of that human's remaining life span.
その人間の残りの寿命の…半分だ
Half of my remaining life span...?
残りの寿命の…半分…
ああ…
In other words, suppose you were to live for another 50 years, that would be reduced to 25 years.
つまり、あと50年生きるとすれば、25年、
あと一年なら半年だ
If you have a year remaining, you get left with half a year.
But currently given that you're not on my side, or on L's side, you won't tell me the names of the people I want to kill?
そして、キラと L のどっちの味方もしないから、
僕の殺したい人間の名前が見えても教えない…
つまり、リュックの力を借りる事はできない
Basically, you're saying that I can't simply borrow your powers... Isn't that right?
そう言いたいんだな
ああ、それは死神界の掟でもあるからな…
Yup. That's one of the rules of the Shinigami world.
もう一度言うぞ
I'll say it once more.
For the price of just half your remaining life span.. you could have the eyes of a Shinigami!
残りの寿命の半分で、死神の目にできる
That way I'll be able to tell the name of anyone I meet just by looking at them!
そうすれば…
顔を見ると全ての人間の名前がわかる…
The Death Note would become even easier to use.
よりデスノートを使いやすくなるというわけか…
So.. What do you want to do, Light?
さぁ…どうする？ライト
To be continued
ここまで忠実に、デスノートに書いた事が再現されるとはね…
ジャスト11時45分、全て予定通り…
デスノートに狂いなし！